[English subtitles are available]
[Song of the Moon]
[Episode 18]
He Na.
The immortal is just taking Fu back to temporary detention.
There will be no problem.
I'm the Demon King.
When I say no,
it means no.
It's a pity.
In the Aquatic Demons,
not all of us listen to the Demon King.
I'll go.
Fu!
In that case,
we'll leave tomorrow morning.
I'll give you one night to say goodbye.
Meet the Immortal Master.
I asked you to keep an eye on Liu Shao
and prevent her from getting too close to Luo Ge.
How could you let them
go to the Demon Palace together?
Immortal Master, please understand.
It was Liu Shao who saw the immortal leave
and followed him.
After all, I didn't know
Xiyin Mountain so well
and not as well treated by the immortal as Liu Shao,
who is close to Fairy Luo Ning.
Everything went easy on her.
I see.
I'll give you a token
with which you can come and go freely in the immortal world.
As for Xiyin Mountain,
I'll also tell Luo Ge
not to stop you.
Thank you, Immortal Master.
Go back.
Don't be so weak.
I'm not that delicate
as your brother.
I can live a good life
everywhere.
Fu can't be out of the water
for more than two hours.
Otherwise, his life will be in danger.
I will take care of that.
Immortal,
you should go back first.
I have something
to say to He Na.
He Na.
I'm sorry.
This
has nothing to do with you.
I don't know
what Fu has to do with the Four Seasons Monument.
Neither do I know
why Lu Sheng
left such a warning before he was gone.
But I know
you are the most innocent one
who has the hardest feelings
in this.
As the demon king of a cursed race,
I'm destined to suffer
these hard feelings and pain.
I don't know what I can do.
But He Na,
I wish I could help you.
Fu is now a prisoner for me.
It's not easy for you to get a foothold in Immortal Palace.
You can't be dragged down by me too.
You won't.
Luo Ge looks cold.
But he won't give me a hard time.
But Luo Ge is not the old Lu Li.
Lu Li
doesn't exist anymore.
The one who took away my family just now
is the heartless, emotionless
but powerful Immortal Luo Ge.
I won't let this happen again.
From now on,
I will strive for
what I want,
whether it's the survival of my people,
or the people I care about.
Do you mean Fu?
And you.
We've been through so much together.
Of course, you are also one of the people I care about the most.
He Na.
Thank you.
I'm always grateful
to have a friend like you.
Where's the pendant I gave you?
It's water hyacinth?
I borrowed some of the power of the Brahma tree.
It can make the pendant more perceptive.
Take it as a thank you
for helping us to awaken the Brahma tree.
He Na.
Thank you.
See you later.
Liu Shao.
You must not know
the only woman who is qualified to use a water hyacinth accessory
is the Demon Queen.
I hope that one day,
I can walk in the sunlight
with my people
to welcome you
as my demon queen.
You're locking me in the middle of the pool
so that I can reach water whenever I want.
It seems
you're not as cruel as I thought.
Brother just let me copy
these useless scriptures and magic techniques.
I guess I can't even
beat the turtle demon in the pool
with these.
There are no turtles in Xiyin Mountain.
You don't need to fight with anyone either.
Brother.
You're finally back.
Have you finished copying the scriptures I assigned you?
No.
I've been copying sutras since I was a kid.
There seems to be no end to it.
Brother.
I heard
you brought a bad guy
back to Xiyin Mountain.
Can I
use him to train spells
and beat him for fun?
No way.
This man is cunning
Don't even think about coming near him.
I've set up a barrier in the place
where he's being held.
If you get within one foot of him,
I will know immediately.
Brother. Brother.
Then, can I have fun in the mortal world?
No, you can't.
Brother.
Can I go to the Palace of Abyssal Mirrors
and learn magic with them?
No, you can't.
Then...
Then, can I focus on the spells
and never be lazy?
It's a deal.
Brother.
It's no fun at all.
Since you are so motivated,
you have ten days
to learn this charm.
That's...
That's so difficult.
If I could learn it,
I'd be the turtle in the pool.
Brother.
What are you doing?
What a coincidence.
The charm I showed you just now
is the key to breaking my ban on you leaving the house.
What?
Brother, you can't do that.
You...
Please let me out!
This is the Tears of the Half-Demon.
It's for you.
I promised you
every time I go out, I will bring you a gift.
Unlike someone in the pool,
I always keep my word.
Brother.
Brother!
Brother, let me out!
Ten thousand years ago,
the Demon King killed the Immortal Ze Shui.
Ten thousand years later,
the Demons are using demon string to cause trouble again,
killing countless innocent people,
almost causing a great disaster.
How can we allow them to continue the rampage?
Immortal, please give your order
to send an army to the Demon Palace
and wipe out the Aquatic Demons.
Master Zhuo.
What do you think?
We practice immortal magic
to protect the three worlds,
not to suppress the weak.
If we have to fight,
we might as well wait for the evidence.
Although our immortals
should have compassion for all beings.
But among the three worlds,
the demon nature is the most uncontrollable.
Since
the demon string is indeed from the lineage of the demon king of the Aquatic Demons,
it is the solid evidence.
We shouldn't let the Aquatic Demons go.
Send the army to the Demon Palace!
Quiet, everyone.
Since Xiyuan Mountain is in charge of the investigation
and Luo Ge is the only Immortal in the Immortal Palace,
let's follow his order.
As is known,
Master Zhuo and I have always been at odds.
But this time,
I'm with Master Zhuo.
We've been cultivating for thousands of years,
aiming to stabilize the three worlds and protect all beings.
The demons can be good too.
Even if there are evil demons with a taste for killing,
the whole demon race shouldn't be involved.
If we don't care about good and evil,
what's the difference between us
and the demons who kill the innocent?
Immortal Master.
Sorry to offend you.
Shang Yurong.
Come out.
Zhuo.
You're looking for me?
There was a discussion on whether to attack the Demon Palace
in the Litian Temple today,
why didn't you come?
You just gave me
the next book of the Great Sword Formation.
Of course I have to practice.
What?
Someone was being mean to you?
Tell me who it is.
I'll teach him a lesson.
That's not true.
But it's rare to see Luo Ge being kind
and agreeing with me
on not attacking the Demon Palace.
That's fine.
If he dares not help you,
I'll confront him later.
You've acquired “Burning Sea”
and dare to fight him now?
You're not afraid of being gagged by him?
Okay, okay.
I'll work hard.
By the way,
this is for you.
What's this?
It's the flower marrow
I found
when practicing the sword in the mountains.
I want you to have it. Try it.
So
while practicing, you went to pick up the flower?
It's not a big deal for me to age.
I don't need you to waste time.
You should've spent the time practicing.
Okay, okay.
From today onwards,
I will work hard.
I will show the whole Immortal Palace
what I'm capable of as the master of the Palace of Abyssal Mirrors.
You can get out.
I'm fine.
Is this about the sword cut you blocked for me?
Is the sword
mixed with
the poisonous energy of the Brahma Lotus
which has made you hurt worse?
It's just a sword wound.
It's already healed.
Since you said it's already healed,
it must be.
So I'll leave now.
Oh.
By the way,
I'll bring in
the medicine I made for you.
Don't come out.
You have to have a good rest.
Be careful.
Heartbeat.
It's Lu Li's heartbeat.
Why are you so stupid?
Lu Li.
Lu Li is still here.
Luo Ge wouldn't remind me.
But Lu Li would.
Luo Ge wouldn't comfort me.
Luo Ge doesn't like people to touch him,
not even the piece of his clothes.
But I can do that to Lu Li.
Do you remember?
Lu Li loved to do this.
You're overthinking it.
It's Lu Li.
Lu Li is back.
I'm not Lu Li.
I'm not.
Master.
[Half-demon Lu Sheng]
It's not true.
Master.
I'm late.
Who was it?
Who did this to you?
Master.
I will not let you
die in vain like this.
I will find the person who did this to you
and make him pay for it.
Master.
I must become stronger.
Even without your help,
I have to establish myself in Immortal Palace
and get Luo Ge back.
Master.
If you're watching over me,
you must help me.
This is the magic weapon
Master used
to hide his demonic aura.
With this,
I'll be able to use
Ao Hen's demon energy
Her Majesty is dead! Run!
Ao Hen's demon energy.
All demons, on my command.
Spread out and collect the spirit energy.
All of you!
I thought the energy belonged to Her Majesty.
Who is she?
That's some tough talk.
I thought Her Majesty had returned.
That's strange.
Isn't this Her Majesty's magic?
Who else wants to die?
We're here
to greet the new king.
Meet the new king.
I will become stronger
and get everything I want,
whether it's Luo Ge or power.
Those who stand in my way,
I will kill them all.
Don't worry about it.
For immortal,
even the gravest of injuries
would take only a night to heal.
There was one time
when I scratched him,
the blood marks on his face were still there the next day.
I wonder if the poison of the Brahma Lotus
is specifically bad for the immortal.
It hurt him so badly.
Don't worry.
The Brahma Lotus can't kill him.
Don't underestimate
my 10,000 years of cultivation.
I've checked it out.
The most amazing thing about Xuan Ling Wood is
[Xuan Ling Wood]
its ability to clear the mind
and keep it pure.
It's the most beneficial treasure for immortal cultivation.
That's a relief.
Clear the mind.
Lu Li.
What exactly did you experience in the mortal world?
How come I've used up all the spiritual power of Xuan Ling Wood
and your distractions still can't be washed away?
Immortal.
Master, please take a look.
What's wrong with him?
I thought you said can recover from the poison by himself
and
the spiritual power of the Xuan Ling Wood
could cure the poison.
It's strange.
How can this happen?
He's not just poisoned.
His wound hasn't healed.
His body has always been able to
heal himself.
But now his immortal power is so weak.
Hasn't he been recuperating in the quiet room?
Now it's like
he he has just been in a fight.
Cut it off.
See how to cure him.
I don't know the cause. How can I cure him?
But
I can use Xuan Ling Wood to remove the poison first.
What...
Why did the Xuan Ling Mu become like this?
Why is it so lethargic?
The leaves are withered.
The wood is nourished by immortal power,
and not by the rain and dew of the earth.
Could it be that the immortal
wanted to use Xuan Ling Wood to get rid of the poison,
but the wood
had a serious lack of spiritual power,
He tried to nourish it with his own immortal power, and depleted it in the process?
so his immortal power got overdrawn?
Should we get the Immortal Master to help?
Are you stupid?
If they knew
the immortal is hurt like this because of you,
they'd kill you.
Besides, their immortal power
is not enough to water the Xuan Ling Wood.
Does this tree have to be watered with immortal power?
Divine spirit
But
there hasn't been a God in 10,000 years
in the Immortal Palace.
What about the divine spirit?
It can't work.
But the boundary
doesn't seem as stable as yesterday.
Could something have happened to Luo Ge?
If that's the case,
it'll be a great opportunity.
There's one more ban on someone else
above the boundary.
It seems that Luo Ge doesn't want someone to come to me.
In this way,
I'd like to meet this person.
Although I can't break the boundary,
this kind of ban
can't hold me back.
It's done.
But
who is this person
that Luo Ge cares so much about?
Xuan Ling Wood is spiritual.
If you try to connect with it spiritually,
and give it your spiritual energy,
it will take in your spiritual power.
But it's a tree after all.
If you can't run your divine spirit freely,
it will empty your spiritual energy.
It's very painful.
You have to be careful.
Liu… Liu Shao.
I'm cold.
Lu Li.
Immortal Luo Ge,
the three palaces have gathered at Litian Hall for a discussion.
The Immortal Master sent me
to ask you if you can be present.
No.
Lu Li.
You have made a sinful bond.
But now it's me who owes her a lot.
How dare these demons to be so reckless?
Marquis Wuyang and Ao Hen
were killed in the Battle of Lusitai.
The mortal and the demon world naturally fall into chaos.
How dare they!
Where do they leave our Immortal Palace?
Don't we have someone decisive in Immortal Palace?
Why do we have to worry?
Immortal Master,
Immortal Luo Ge doesn't want to come.
He... he...
What's wrong with him?
He's at Liu Shao's bedside for some reason.
for a day and a night.
And no one else is allowed to enter,
not even me.
I seem to have had a dream again.
I dreamt of Lu Li.
No.
It's Luo Ge.
Immortal Luo Ge.
Are you feeling better?
I'm fine.
I need to thank you for this.
You know about it?
Some of the spiritual power
in your divine spirit was taken away,
it was painful.
But it's not a bad thing for you.
The spiritual energy you re-cultivate
integrates better with yourself.
The power of the God of the Sun
can hopefully become your own.
In that case,
I've been blessed by a disaster.
Open your mouth.
What is that?
The pill
is made from many medicinal herbs
combined with the spiritual energy of Xuan Ling Wood.
It's beneficial
for your cultivation.
The spiritual energy of Xuan Ling Wood?
What are you doing?
The spiritual energy of Xuan Ling Wood
can cleanse one's mind.
Should I
cut off my thoughts about you…
About Lu Li then?
No way.
I can't forget Lu Li
even if I die.
You won't forget him.
If you love him so much,
all the power of Xuan Ling Wood
won't be able to wipe off the feelings in the slightest.
But worldly love is so stubborn and uninteresting.
It only causes trouble
when you fall deeper into it.
You are uninteresting.
Being in the three worlds,
I've seen all beings
and cleansed my mind.
I am uninteresting.
You should meet interesting people
who you have more in common with,
so that you won't be confined.
Immortal Luo Ge,
Lu Li is the interesting person
who has a lot in common with me.
You said I couldn't touch you,
not even a piece of your clothes.
But why
did you allow me
to grab your sleeve for the whole night?
Luo Ge.
Thank you.
You protected me
all night long.
That's not true.
I just
never owe anyone.
Wait for me.
Immortal,
the Immortal Master sent me to ask you for advice.
The demons have aroused a sudden calamity in the mortal world.
I wonder if you can go there to quell the demons.
Go back and tell the Immortal Master.
I will go.
Yes.
Immortal,
although the poison of Brahma Lotus has been removed,
you haven't fully recovered from the wound.
You shouldn't go out now.
Many people were not happy with me
when I defended the demons
in Litian Hall.
I don't care about this.
But Immortal Master does.
He is my master.
I can't put him in this.
I'll go with you then.
You?
I come from the mortal world.
Maybe I can help you.
As you please.
Wait for me.
[Mansion of Wu Yang Duke]
Xue.
Jian.
Kill these two people.
Suck out the vitality.
Give it to the new king.
Who is your new king?
Xue.
Moon…
Moon Sword?
Is…
Is this Immortal Luo Ge?
Xue.
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
Who is your new king?
Answer my question.
Who
is your new king?
I…
I can't say.
If I do,
the new king will make us die horribly.
I heard
you've killed many of the disciples in the Mansion of Wu Yang Duke.
You crossed the world to kill people
and reached the Mansion of Wu Yang Duke.
Where do you leave the Immortal Palace?
You're their new king?
No.
Then why do you come here?
Thank you for saving my whole clan from death
in the Palace of Abyssal Mirrors.
At the same time,
I want to inform you of something.
What is it?
The Aquatic Demons
were once the kings of the entire demon realm.